thank you for about a minute and ask u
questions color in this collected and
what is the like when you speaking only
with pocket so tell me where you felt
and dementia which is uh... agra gravity
and and it is still in existence added
uh... olive branch yes
and lighting the switches
pat there is my grandfather who is
anglophone and my uncle info in them
their their and went in
inning
and was working as a prediction in this
country from her first vasai was
practicing all summer
and uh...
the family
soup they do
hap at my sister
rather all all today
believes is the biggest difference union
uh... everywhere educated because then
i was raised with my mom and and they
were responding with their moms
whether it's the law
dylan